<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News | Fengyue Zhao</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>News</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu_88080d99dd003e3b.png</url>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>🗣️ I’m presenting at Interspeech 2025 in Rotterdam!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025interspeech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025interspeech/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m excited to present my paper &amp;ldquo;The Role of Contextual Variation in Learning Cantonese Tones from Naturalistic Speech&amp;rdquo;, co-authored with Dr. Jennifer Kuo, at the 26th edition of the Interspeech Conference (Interspeech 2025), held in Rotterdam, The Netherlands from August 17–21.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to sharing our findings and connecting with fellow researchers in speech science!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🗣️ I gave a podium talk at the Boston Speech Motor Control Symposium!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025bsmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025bsmc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In June 2025, I presented my research titled &amp;ldquo;Unpredictable Temporal Auditory Feedback Perturbation Induces Lengthening, Not Compensation&amp;rdquo;, co-authored with Dr. Sam Tilsen, at the 5th Biennial Boston Speech Motor Control Symposium (BSMCS’25), hosted at Boston University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was grateful to receive a Student Travel Award from the Boston Speech Motor Control Symposium to support my participation in this event.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🗣️ I gave a talk at TAI 2025!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025tai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025tai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In May 2025, I presented my talk &amp;ldquo;Distributional Learning Across Contexts: Learning Cantonese Tones in Naturalistic Speech&amp;rdquo;, co-authored with Dr. Jennifer Kuo, at the 3rd International Conference on Tone and Intonation (TAI 2025), held at the Institute for Phonetics and Speech Processing, Ludwig-Maximilians-Universität in Munich, Germany.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m thankful to the International Phonetic Association for supporting my participation with an IPA Student Award, which helped make this international travel possible.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎉 I passed my second qualifying exam and became a phd candidate!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025a-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025a-exam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In May 2025, I successfully passed my second qualifying exam and officially advanced to PhD candidacy in Linguistics at Cornell University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My dissertation is titled &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Role of Contextual Variation in Learning Cantonese Tones from Naturalistic Speech.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My committee consists of Professor Jennifer Kuo (Co-Chair), Professor Marten van Schijndel (Co-Chair), and Professor Samuel Tilsen.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
